busygirlblog.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy – busygirlblog

Our team here at Busygirlblog is fully committed to protecting all our users privacy online. By continuing to use this site, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to all terms stated in this policy.

### General

Our users are free to visit and enjoy our content at no personal obligation; users can exit the site whenever they so choose and do not need to reveal any personal information about themselves. There are some services offered that users may want to take advantage of, and it’s possible they will be required to disclose some personal information, including but not limited to, their first and last name, home address, email address, telephone numbers and birthday. It is also possible that other information will be collected on other applicable pages within our sites. If any users do choose to submit information to us directly or to a third party via our site, they can be assured that we will never sell or lease their personal information except;

  1. for special promotions which may be offered on occasion on our sites in conjunction with a third party service provider in order to fullfill any deals or promotions that the user signed up for
  2. to third party service providers we have partnered with so we may provide services our users requested
  3. following a notice posted on a relevant page on our site that collects personal information following a transaction that notifies the user and discloses the purchase

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Disclosure of User Information for Legal Purposes

Federal and state laws requires that from time to time we may be obligated to share personal user information (review Cookies section) that are pursuant to judicial subpoenas or warrants. We also reserve the right to use and share personal information we collect in order to investigate and prevent any activity deemed illegal, fraudulent or may cause physical harm to another person.

### External Links

Our site’s pages will contain links to third party websites that be be unrelated to the content we have created and own. Please understand that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any and all third party companies and websites. It is always recommended to review the privacy policies of all websites you enter to ensure you are fully protected under the law.

### Children

Federal law mandates that we cannot collect any personally identifiable information that originates from a child under the age of thirteen without full consent from that child’s parent of guardian. Therefore we will never collect any information if we know or deem the user to be under the age of thirteen.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.
